{
    "playersIndiv": [
        {
            "id": 8602,
            "info": [
                {
                    "question": "Home town",
                    "answer": "Amsterdam",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Current city ",
                    "answer": "London",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "National teams",
                    "answer": "Played for the Dutch under 24 side in Germany in 2019, Euro beach in 2019",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 17373,
            "info": [
                {
                    "question": "Team",
                    "answer": "Fakers (Mixed)",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How should we refer to you on the field",
                    "answer": "Jeffer",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Current city/town",
                    "answer": "Nottingham",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Age ",
                    "answer": "45",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Height",
                    "answer": "7 foot",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Throwing hand",
                    "answer": "Right handed",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why did you start playing Ultimate?",
                    "answer": "Patrick said I should in 1994",
                    "answerType": "Long"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 8607,
            "info": [
                {
                    "question": "Team",
                    "answer": "Fakers (Mixed)",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How should we refer to you on the field",
                    "answer": "Pete",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Spell your name how it sounds",
                    "answer": "Fuller",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Current city/town",
                    "answer": "Berlin",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Home city/town",
                    "answer": "Stuttgart",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Occupation ",
                    "answer": "Engineer",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Age ",
                    "answer": "31",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Height",
                    "answer": "185cm",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Throwing hand",
                    "answer": "Right handed",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why did you start playing Ultimate?",
                    "answer": "My brother played at school and taught me how to play in the holidays. Soon we were doing it every weekend and I loved every minute. ",
                    "answerType": "Long"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many years have you been playing?",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "answerType": "Short"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which school/university team(s) have you played for?",
                    "answer": "Big Town School",
                    "answerType": "Long"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which club team(s) have you played for? ",
                    "answer": "Big Town Heros",
                    "answerType": "Long"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which national team(s) have you played for?",
                    "answer": "Germany Mixed Beach (2018) Germany Indoor (2017)",
                    "answerType": "Long"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What has been the highlight of your Ultimate playing career? ",
                    "answer": "Winning the national question with Big Town Heros",
                    "answerType": "Long"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}